[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "blue",
        "back": "синий",
        "setName": "Color"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "green",
        "back": "зеленый",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "pink",
        "back": "розовый",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "mouse",
        "back": "мышь",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "cat",
        "back": "кошка",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "dog",
        "back": "собака",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "black",
        "back": "черный",
        "setName": "Color"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "tea",
        "back": "чай",
        "setName": "English"
    }
]